question_data = [

    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The average woman is 5 inches / 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
